Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files K-O, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Amsterdam News photograph archive, 1920-2012.
8084
New York Amsterdam News.
189 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Photographs, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes photographs and related materials covering a broad range of topics, with a particular focus on day-to-day life in New York's African-American community during the 20th century.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Founded in 1909 by James H. Anderson, the New York Amsterdam News is one of the oldest African-American owned and run newspapers in the country. Initially focused on local news in New York in general and Harlem in particular, the Amsterdam News broadened its scope to include national news under the guidance of editor Dr. C.B. Powell in the 1930s. By the 1960s, the newspaper had become a major voice in the national African-American community, offering extensive coverage of the civil rights movement. Beginning in 1982, the newspaper was edited by Wilbert A. Tatum, under whose guidance the newspaper remained a voice in local and national affairs. In 1996, Tatum turned control of the newspaper over to his daughter, Elinor Tatum, who remained the publisher and editor-in-chief through the 2000s.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes photographs and related materials covering a broad range of topics, with a particular focus on day-to-day life in New York's African-American community during the 20th century. Subjects include civil rights marches and protests, church events, high school graduations, local politics, and fashion. Some photographs were taken by staff photographers, while others originated with wire services or as submissions from individuals or agencies. Formats in the collection include silver gelatin prints, negatives (including many unpublished images), contact sheets, Polaroids, wire photos, and halftone prints. As the working photo archive of a continuously-published newspaper, many of the images have retouching, attached captions, press releases, cover letters, and printer's instructions. In addition to photographs, the collection includes ephemera and manuscript material, including newspaper article drafts, typescript and mimeographed speeches, correspondence, event programs, magazine and newspaper clippings, employment applications, press releases, and newspaper production materials.
The bulk of the materials in the archive range from the mid-1940s through the mid-1990s. The materials are divided into series, reflecting the organization of the materials in the AM News offices. A major sub-series of the collection is the archive of Mel Tapley, who began working for the Amsterdam News in 1942 and served as entertainment editor until his retirement in 1997. The Mel Tapley archive includes a wide variety of material, including correspondence, manuscript and typescript articles and notes, artwork, press kits, publicity photos, and printing plates for comic strips drawn by Tapley.
Photographers represented in the collection include Bert Andrews, Kwame Brathwaite, Al Burley, James C. Campbell, Curt Clemons, Juanita M. Cole, Karl Crutchfield, L. St. Clair Dummett, Monroe S. Frederick II, James Gilbert, Dave Greene, Austin Hansen, Tex Harris, Bob Head, Cecil Layne, David McAdams, Bill Moore, Allen Morgan, Vondel Nichols, Lem Peterkin, George M. West, and Lloyd Yearwood. Photo agencies and services represented include Pictorial Enterprise, Wide World Photo, Harris Photo, News Voice International, Rapid News Photo, United Press International, Negro Press Photo Service, Wagner International Photos, and Ace Creative Photos.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York Amsterdam News.
Titles:
New York Amsterdam news.
Subjects:
African American newspapers.; African Americans -- New York (State) -- New York.
Places:
New York (N.Y.); Harlem (New York, N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Because of the size of this collection, the guide is broken up into several different pages. Each page is then further separated into different series. The majority of the sereis titles come from titles given by the Amsterdam News.
Main Guide Content Listing
Series A. Main photo sequence
The main alphabetic sequence of prints containing material from 1920-2012 with the bulk being 1944-1996.
Subject files A
Subject files B
Subject files C
Subject files D
Subject files E
Subject files F
Subject files G
Subject files H
Subject files I
Subject files J
Subject files K
Subject files L
Subject files M
Subject files N
Subject files O
Subject files P
Subject files Q
Subject files R
Subject files S
Subject files T
Subject files U
Subject files V
Subject files W
Subject files X
Subject files Y
Subject files Z
Series B. Inactive File
File of inactive, defunct, or deceased individuals and organizations. Bulk material dates from before 1980.
Series C. Presorted Photos
A roughly sorted series of photos.
Series D. Semi Alphabetized Photos
A second roughly sorted series of photos. Most date from 1980-1999.
Series E. Dated Folders
Photos from the 1990s sorted by date.
Series F. Sports Photos
Mostly promotional photos from sports teams.
Series G. Contemporary File
An alphabetic sequence of photos primarily from 1988-2000, but with some older material.
Series H. Transfer File
An alphabetic sequence of topical files with bulk material dates from the 1960s-1970s.
Series I. Dead Photo File
Photos from the 2000s organized by date of their publication in the Amsterdam News.
Series J. Loose Unsorted Items
Unsorted items found in various locations around the Amsterdam News office.
Series MT. Mel Tapley Collection
The personal archive of Mel Tapley, who began working at the Amsterdam News in 1942 and served as the entertainment editor until 1997. Includes a wide variety of ephemera, artwork, manuscript and typescript material, and correspondence.
Miscellaneous Mailings and Press Files
Mel Tapley Artwork
Unsorted Photos
Press Mailings
Books and Booklets
Press Kits
Press Releases
Oversize and Fax Press Releases
Periodicals, Newspapers, Magazines
Audio and Visual Media
CONTAINER LIST
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files K
    - Kaba, West (Box A-68, Folder 204)
      Number of Prints: 1
    - Kabuleta, Francis (Rev.) (Box A-68, Folder 205)
    - Kagombe, M. David (Box A-68, Folder 206)
    - Kahan, Richad A. (Box A-68, Folder 207)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Theo Westenberger
    - Kahlbough, George (Rev.) (Box A-68, Folder 208)
    - Kain, Gylan (Box A-68, Folder 209)
      Photographer if identified: Friedman-Abeles
      Number of Prints: 4
    - Kaiser, Gerald (Box A-68, Folder 210)
      Number of Prints: 2
    - Kaiser, Inez (Box A-68, Folder 211)
      Two prints are stuck together with paste; two have single-leaf press releases attached.
      Photographer if identified: Swetnam & Grier
      Number of Prints: 12
    - Kairson, Urseline (Box A-68, Folder 212)
    - Kalanzi, Benny (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 213)
    - Kalibu, Layding (Box A-68, Folder 214)
    - Kalibola, Evelyn (Box A-68, Folder 215)
    - Kalisch, Marcos (Box A-68, Folder 216)
    - Kallan, Florence (Box A-68, Folder 217)
    - Kalunda, Shirley (Box A-68, Folder 218)
    - Kam, Dick (Box A-68, Folder 219)
    - Kamanyn, Claver (Box A-68, Folder 220)
    - Kamara, Akiki (Box A-68, Folder 221)
    - Kamara, Ermon D. (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 222)
      Print has typescript press release (four leaves) attached with paperclip. Also one velox print.
    - Kamera, Willy David (Box A-68, Folder 223)
    - Kampbell, Joann (Box A-68, Folder 224)
      One velox print.
    - Kamau, James (Box A-68, Folder 225)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise
    - Kan, Dylan (Box A-68, Folder 226)
    - Kandeto, Vezera (Box A-68, Folder 227)
    - Kane, Jacqueline A. (Box A-68, Folder 228)
      Also one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Selean Koury
    - Kane, Larry (Box A-68, Folder 229)
    - Kane, Phillip G. (Box A-68, Folder 230)
      Print is stuck to folder with paste.
    - Kani, Janis (Box A-68, Folder 231)
      Photographer if identified: Sy Presten Associates
    - "Kansas Fried Chicken" (Box A-68, Folder 232)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo
    - Kant, David B. (Box A-68, Folder 233)
    - Kanza, Thomas (Box A-68, Folder 234)
      Print has single typescript leaf attached.
      Photographer if identified: Scurlock Studio
    - Kaplan, Flora (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 235)
    - Kaamil, Rasheek (Box A-68, Folder 236)
    - Kaplan, Kivie (Box A-68, Folder 237)
      Photographer if identified: J. Edward Bailey III, Cecil Layne, David McAdams
      Number of Prints: 9
    - Kappa Omican (Box A-68, Folder 238)
      Photographer if identified: Monroe S. Frederick, Newell Johnson
      Number of Prints: 5
    - Kappa Sigma Chapter (Box A-68, Folder 239)
    - Kappner, Augusta S. (Box A-68, Folder 240)
      Photographer if identified: Gene Luttenberg
    - Karenga, Ron (Box A-68, Folder 241)
    - Karfa, Robin (Box A-68, Folder 242)
      Print has single typescript leaf resume adhered on verso.
    - Karim, Sutton (Box A-68, Folder 243)
    - Kariuki, Joshia M. (Box A-68, Folder 244)
    - Kareem, Haliemah (Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 245)
      Photographer if identified: Dummett
    - "Karma Club" (Box A-68, Folder 246)
      Photographer if identified: James C. Campbell
    - Karnegay, Alice (Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 247)
    - Karnon, Elias (Box A-68, Folder 248)
    - Karol, Karen (Box A-68, Folder 249)
    - Karr, Yolanda (Box A-68, Folder 250)
    - Kasandra, John (Box A-68, Folder 251)
    - Kashi, Aliza (Box A-68, Folder 252)
    - Kashi, Charles (Box A-68, Folder 253)
      Photographer if identified: Lloyd Yearwood
    - Kashino, Dorothe (Box A-68, Folder 254)
      Photographer if identified: James C. Campbell, A. Hansen Studio, A. Keno-Foto
    - Katzenbach, Nicholas D. (Box A-68, Folder 255)
      Note on folder: "See Wallace, George."
      Photographer if identified: United Press International Photos
    - Kaufman, Monica J. (Box A-68, Folder 256)
    - Kaufman, Vi (Box A-68, Folder 257)
      Also three velox prints.
    - Kaunda, Kenneth D. (Box A-68, Folder 258)
      Also one velox print. Two prints have single typescript leaves attached.
      Photographer if identified: Ronnie Brathwaite, Official Photographer of the White House,
      Number of Prints: 14
    - Karouma, Mariki (Box A-68, Folder 259)
      Note on folder: "See Ram."
    - Kauvar, Abraham J. (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 260)
      Number of Prints: 3
    - Kave, Ken (Box A-68, Folder 261)
    - Kawaida Towers Inc. (Box A-68, Folder 262)
      One print has single typescript leaf letter attached with paperclip.
    - Kay, Monte (Box A-68, Folder 263)
    - Kay, Tony (Box A-68, Folder 264)
    - Kay, Ulysses (Box A-68, Folder 265)
      single-leaf press release.
    - Kay, Pamela (Box A-68, Folder 266)
    - Kaye, Cab (Box A-68, Folder 267)
      Photographer if identified: Maurey Garber
    - Kaye, Danny (Box A-68, Folder 268)
    - Kayibanda, Gregory (Box A-68, Folder 269)
    - Kea, Morris (Box A-68, Folder 270)
      Print has single typescript leaf attached with paperclip.
    - Keahy, Robert Jr. (Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 271)
    - Kean, Dan (Box A-68, Folder 272)
      One print has single typescript leaf attached with paperclip.
    - Kearing, Samuel J. Jr. Commissioner (Box A-68, Folder 273)
    - Kearney, Maurice B. (Box A-68, Folder 274)
    - Kearney, Wm. H. (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 275)
    - Kearse, Amalya (Box A-68, Folder 276)
    - Kearse, Emma L. (Box A-68, Folder 277)
    - Kearse, John (Box A-68, Folder 278)
    - Kearse, Lee A. (Box A-68, Folder 279)
    - Keaser, Lloyd W. (Butch) Lt. (Box A-68, Folder 280)
    - Kearse, Rose (Box A-68, Folder 281)
    - Keating, Kenneth (Senator) (Box A-68, Folder 282)
      One print has single-leaf press release attached with staple on border.
    - Keats, Leroy (Box A-68, Folder 283)
    - Kee, John P. (Box A-68, Folder 284)
    - Keel, Mildred Y. (Box OS-1, Folder 2)
    - Keene, Jerrilyn (Box A-68, Folder 285)
    - Kee, Salaria (Box A-69, Folder 1)
      One print is cut out and mounted on board.
      Photographer if identified: Continental News Photographers
    - Keeling, Shelley (Box A-69, Folder 2)
    - Keels, Avant (Box A-69, Folder 3)
    - Keene, Robert L. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-69, Folder 4)
    - Keeshan, Bob (Box A-69, Folder 5)
    - Kefauver, Estes (Mrs.) (Box A-69, Folder 6)
    - Keino, Kipchoge (Box A-69, Folder 7)
      Photographer if identified: United Press International Photo
    - Keiser, Kris (Box A-69, Folder 8)
    - Keita, Modibo (Box A-69, Folder 9)
      Note on folder: "President of Mali."
      Photographer if identified: Pan American World Airways
    - Keith, Augustus (Box A-69, Folder 10)
    - Keith, Damon Judge (Box A-69, Folder 11)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos
    - Keith, Emanuel (Box A-69, Folder 12)
    - Keith, Ethel (Mrs.) (Box A-69, Folder 13)
    - Keith, Harold L. (Box A-69, Folder 14)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Angency for International Development
    - Keith, Herman (Box A-69, Folder 15)
    - Kellar, Charles (Box A-69, Folder 16)
      Photographer if identified: Herbert Hawkins, The Bing Studio
    - Kellam, Leroy B. (Box A-69, Folder 17)
    - Kelleher, Hugh (Box A-69, Folder 18)
    - Keller, Mavis Elaine (Box A-69, Folder 19)
    - Kellman, Denis E. (Box A-69, Folder 20)
    - Kelley, Babara Jean (Box A-69, Folder 21)
      Photographer if identified: Emma Rivera
    - Kelley, Carolyn (Box A-69, Folder 22)
      Photographer if identified: Art Photo Studio
    - Kelley, Charles H. (Dr.) (Box A-69, Folder 23)
    - Kelley, Ernie (Box A-69, Folder 24)
    - Kelley, Garrye Hill (Box A-69, Folder 25)
    - Kelley, Hilton B. (Box A-69, Folder 26)
      Note on verso of print: "Alleged slayer of Beverly Perkins."
    - Kelley, Jim (Box A-69, Folder 27)
    - Kelley, LeVirt (Box A-69, Folder 28)
    - Kelley, Lucinda (Box A-69, Folder 29)
    - Kelley, Mr. & Mrs. (Rev.) (Box A-69, Folder 30)
    - Kellogg, Junius (Box A-69, Folder 31)
      Photographer if identified: Pan American World Airways, Photography by Wilson, Harris Photo, Bahamas News Bureau Photo, Harris Photo
      Number of Prints: 6
    - Kelly, Adrienne L. (Box A-69, Folder 32)
    - Kelly, Agnes (Box A-69, Folder 33)
    - Kelly, Cecelia (Box A-69, Folder 34)
    - Kelly, Colleen (Box A-69, Folder 35)
      Print is cut out and mounted on paper.
    - Kelly, Donald (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-69, Folder 36)
      Photographer if identified: Oscar Mallory
    - Kelly, F. (Box A-69, Folder 37)
    - Kelly, Fanny (Box A-69, Folder 38)
      Print is adhered to a piece of cardstock with staples on border.
    - Kelly, Florida L. (Box A-69, Folder 39)
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers
    - Kelly, George, Sr. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-69, Folder 40)
    - Kelly, Grace (Mrs.) (Box A-69, Folder 41)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen Studio
    - Kelly, Howard (Elder & Mrs.) (Box A-69, Folder 42)
    - Kelly, Irvin Lee (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-69, Folder 43)
    - Kelly, J. Dvaid (Rev.) (Box A-69, Folder 44)
      Photographer if identified: Harold Stovall Studio
    - Kelly, Jacqueline S. (Box A-69, Folder 45)
    - Kelly, James Bishop (Box A-69, Folder 46)
      Photographer if identified: Pope Studio
    - Kelly, James C., Sr. (Rev.) (Box A-69, Folder 47)
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers, Dave Greene
    - Kelly, James E. (Box A-69, Folder 48)
    - Kelly, James O. (Box A-69, Folder 49)
      One print is cut out and mounted on paper.
    - Kelly, Janice (Box A-69, Folder 50)
    - Kelly, Jim (Box A-69, Folder 51)
    - Kelly, Jimmy (Box A-69, Folder 52)
    - Kelly, John (Box A-69, Folder 53)
    - Kelly, Joseph (Box A-69, Folder 54)
    - Kelly, Julia (Box A-69, Folder 55)
    - Kelly, June (Box A-69, Folder 56)
      One print reads "Best Wishes Black Teenage America 1971."
    - Kelly, Lisa (Box A-69, Folder 57)
    - Kelly, Lloyd (Box A-69, Folder 58)
    - Kelly, Jennie Marie (Box A-69, Folder 59)
      Photographer if identified: White's Photo Farm Production
    - Kelly, O. B. (Chief Steward) (Box A-69, Folder 60)
      Photographer if identified: Keystone Pictures Inc.
    - Kelly, O. M. (Box A-69, Folder 61)
      Also one velox print. One print has newspaper clipping adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Ernest C. Withers, Nichols
      Number of Prints: 8
    - Kelly, Owen, Bishop (Box A-69, Folder 62)
    - Kelly, Paula (Box A-69, Folder 63)
      One print has one-paragraph typescript description on verso.
    - Kelly, Philip J. (Box A-69, Folder 64)
    - Kelly, Teddy (Box A-69, Folder 65)
      Print has "Teddy Kelly and Baby Lawrence" in ms. writing on recto.
    - Kelly, W.C. (Box A-69, Folder 66)
      Photographer if identified: Nichols, Dummett
    - Kelly, William (Box A-69, Folder 67)
      Print has single-leaf press release attached.
    - Kelly, William (Mrs.) (Box A-69, Folder 68)
    - Kelly, Wynton C. (Pvt.) (Box A-69, Folder 69)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Army Photographer
    - Kelly, Wynton (Trio) (Box A-69, Folder 70)
    - Kelly, Yvonne (Box A-69, Folder 71)
      Photographer if identified: Trans World Airlines
    - Kelsick, Anthony X. (Box A-69, Folder 72)
    - Kelty, Joe (Box A-69, Folder 73)
    - Kemp, Emma (Box A-69, Folder 74)
      One print has single-leaf press release adhered on verso.
    - Kelsey, A. R. (Mr.) (Box A-69, Folder 75)
    - Kelsey, Everett (Box A-69, Folder 76)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert
    - Kelsey, George D. (Box A-69, Folder 77)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix with single-leaf press release attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Aristocrat Studio
    - Kelson, Lucille (Box A-69, Folder 78)
      Photographer if identified: Dalman James Jr.
    - Kemms, Willie J. (Dr.) (Box A-69, Folder 79)
    - Kemp, Carolyn T. (Box A-69, Folder 80)
    - Kemp, Emme (Box A-69, Folder 81)
    - Kemp, Harrison (Box A-69, Folder 82)
      Print has newspaper clipping adhered on verso.
    - Kemp, Herbert (Box A-69, Folder 83)
    - Kemp, Herbert Jr. (Box A-69, Folder 84)
    - Kemp, John W. (Box A-69, Folder 85)
      Also one clipping with photo from a print publication.
    - Kemp, Maida Springer (Box A-69, Folder 86)
      Photographer if identified: George Bing
    - Kemp, Sparkle (Box A-69, Folder 87)
    - Kemp, Shirley (Box A-69, Folder 88)
      Note on folder: "& son Ira."
    - Kemp, Meatta (Box A-69, Folder 89)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert/News Voice International
    - Kemp, Ruth (Box A-69, Folder 90)
    - Kemp, Tyrone (Box A-69, Folder 91)
      Photographer if identified: Norman Franke
    - Kempen, Carl (Box A-69, Folder 92)
    - Kendall, Michael (Box A-69, Folder 93)
    - Kendrick, Cutis (Dr.) (Box A-69, Folder 94)
      Photographer if identified: The Bing Studio
    - Kendricks, Eddie (Box A-69, Folder 95)
      Also two velox prints. One print has carbonscript biography (five leaves, stapled) attached with a paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Visual Images/Chas. Tilley, W-ABC TV Photos
    - Kendricks, Edgar (Box A-69, Folder 96)
      Photo has single-leaf press release attached with staple on border.
    - Kenricks, Wm. (Box A-69, Folder 97)
    - Kenin, Herman (Box A-69, Folder 98)
      Print has single typescript leaf adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Merkle Press
    - Kennard, Ann (Box A-69, Folder 99)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Carter
    - Kennard, Dick (Jr.) (Box A-69, Folder 100)
      See "Kennard, Richard Jr."
    - Kennard, Richard C. (Box A-69, Folder 101)
      Also one velox print. One print has two single-leaf press releases attached with paperclip.
    - Kennard, Ron (Box A-69, Folder 102)
    - Kennedy, Adrienne (Box A-69, Folder 103)
    - Kennedy, Agnes (Box A-69, Folder 104)
    - Kennedy, Ethel (Box A-69, Folder 105)
      Photographer if identified: Dan Miller, Harris Photo
    - Kennedy, Alanda D. (Box A-69, Folder 106)
    - Kennedy, Art, Jr. (Box A-69, Folder 107)
    - Kennedy, Betty (Box A-69, Folder 108)
    - Kennedy, Bill (Box A-69, Folder 109)
    - Kennedy, Bob (Box A-69, Folder 110)
    - Kennedy, Bobby, Jr. (Box A-69, Folder 111)
    - Kennedy, Carolyn Cantor (Box A-69, Folder 112)
    - Kennedy, Claire (Box A-69, Folder 113)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne
    - Kennedy, Earl (Box A-69, Folder 114)
    - Kennedy, Edward (Box A-69, Folder 115)
      Photographer if identified: Creative Photography
    - Kennedy, Geri (Box A-69, Folder 116)
    - Kennedy, Helen Wilson (Box A-69, Folder 117)
    - Kennedy, Jacqueline Bouvier (Box A-69, Folder 118)
      One print has single typescript leaf attached.
    - Kennedy, Dr. James (Box A-69, Folder 119)
    - Kennedy, Jay Richard (Box A-69, Folder 120)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Kennedy, Jayne (Box A-69, Folder 121)
      Number of Prints: 13
    - Kennedy, Joann (Box A-69, Folder 122)
    - Kennedy, John F., Jr. (Box A-69, Folder 123)
    - Kennedy, John F. Community Center (Box A-69, Folder 124)
    - John F. Kennedy Center For International Education (Box A-69, Folder 125)
      Print has single typescript leaf description adhered on verso.
    - Kennedy, Joseph (Box A-69, Folder 126)
    - Kennedy, Joseph P. (Community Center) (Box A-69, Folder 127)
      One print has single-leaf press release attached.
    - Kennedy, Joy (Box A-69, Folder 128)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Carter, Ace Creative Photos, Dalman James Jr., Tex Harris
      Number of Prints: 7
    - Kennedy, Kenneth (Box A-69, Folder 129)
    - Kennedy, Leon (Box A-69, Folder 130)
    - Kennedy, Lorraine C. Holmes (Box A-69, Folder 131)
    - Kennedy, Marguerite (Box A-69, Folder 132)
      Photographer if identified: Irving Kaufman
    - Kennedy, Matthew (Box A-69, Folder 133)
    - Kennedy Plaza (Box A-69, Folder 134)
    - Kennedy, Richard (Box A-69, Folder 135)
    - Kennedy, Robert (Box A-69, Folder 136)
      Note on folder: "See Inactive File." Print is cut out and damaged.
    - Kennedy, Robert (Mrs.) (Box A-69, Folder 137)
    - Kennedy, Mrs. Rose (Box A-69, Folder 138)
      Photographer if identified: Cuttino
    - Kennedy, Stanley (Box A-69, Folder 139)
    - Kennedy, Theodore (Ted) (Box A-69, Folder 140)
      Also one cut-out from a print publication featuring photo of Martin Luther King Jr.
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene, James Gilbert, United Press International Photo
    - Kennedy, Walter (Box A-69, Folder 141)
      Also two velox prints.
    - Kennedy, William, Jr. (Box A-69, Folder 142)
      Photographer if identified: Bruce Stromberg, Harris Photo
    - Kennell, Edward F. (Box A-69, Folder 143)
      One print has single-leaf press release attached with paperclip.
    - Kennelly, Martin H. (Mayor-elect) (Box A-69, Folder 144)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert V. Brown
    - Kennely, Sharna (Box A-69, Folder 145)
      Back of print reads: "Missing."
    - Kenney, Alexis R. (Box A-69, Folder 146)
    - Kenney, Bruce (Box A-69, Folder 147)
    - Kenney, Clarence (Box A-69, Folder 148)
    - Kenney, Howard W. (Dr.) (Box A-69, Folder 149)
      Print has typescript press release (two leaves) attached on border.
    - Kenney, Jerry (Box A-69, Folder 150)
    - Kenney, John (Dr.) (Box A-69, Folder 151)
      Photographer if identified: M. Baier/Salov Photographer
    - Kenny, Herbert (Box A-69, Folder 152)
    - Kenny, John A. (Dr.) (Box A-69, Folder 153)
      Print has single-leaf press release attached with paperclip.
    - Kenny, John E. (Dr.) (Box A-69, Folder 154)